https://www.aearibbonmics.com/privacy-policy/

AEARibbonMics.com Privacy PolicyThis Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from www.aearibbonmics.com (the “Site”).This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally Identifiable Information’ (PII) is being used online. PII, as described in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context.Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website?When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address, phone number or other details to help you with your experience.When using the contact form, we collect typical “business card information” such as your first and last name, email address, telephone number.When using the repair form, we collect typical “business card information” in addition to information about your product you intend to service.When using the warranty form, we collect typical “business card information” in addition to your company name, website or social media handle, the information about the product you are registering, as well as comments about your purchase experience, and other comments.When do we collect information?We collect information from you when you register a product on our site, use the contact form, subscribe to a newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a repair form, or open a Support Ticket on our site.How do we use your information?We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:• To improve our website in order to better serve you.• To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.• To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.• To quickly process your transactions.• To send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services.• To follow up with them after correspondence (live chat, email or phone inquiries)How do we use Social Media Widgets?Some parts of our Service may include social media features, such as the Facebook “like” button, and widgets, such as the “share this” button. These social media features are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Service. When you use these tools, the party that provides the tool, the third party that operates the social media services.How do we protect your information?Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.Do we use ‘cookies’?We do not use cookies for tracking purposes.You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since each browser is a little different, look at your browser’s Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.Third-party disclosureWe will never sell or trade your information to outside parties.We may share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.Third-party linksOccasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We, therefore, have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.Use of Credit Card InformationIf you give us credit card information, we use it solely to check your financial qualifications and collect payment from you. We use a third-party service provider to manage credit card processing. This service provider is not permitted to store, retain, or use the information you provide except for the sole purpose of credit card processing on our behalf.GoogleWe have implemented the following:• Demographics and Interests ReportingThird-party vendors such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.Opting out:Users can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative Opt-Out page or by using the Google Analytics Opt-Out Browser add-on.European ResidentsAEA is committed to compliance with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), a new EU data privacy regulation that will go into effect May 25, 2018. The regulation is designed to give EU citizens more control over their data and to unify a number of existing privacy and security laws under one comprehensive law.If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, rectified, exported, updated, or deleted.If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.California Online Privacy Protection ActCalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law’s reach stretches well beyond California to require any person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting Personally Identifiable Information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals or companies with whom it is being shared. – See more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpufAccording to CalOPPA, we agree to the following:Users can visit our site anonymously.Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or as a minimum, on the first significant page after entering our website.Privacy Policy LinkOur Privacy Policy link includes the word ‘Privacy’ and can easily be found on the page specified above.You will be notified of any Privacy Policy changes:• On our Privacy Policy PageCan change your personal information:• By emailing usHow does our site handle Do Not Track signals?We honor Do Not Track signals and Do Not Track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?It’s also important to note that we do not allow third-party behavioral tracking.COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under the age of 13 years old, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, United States’ consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online.We do not specifically market to children under the age of 13 years old.Fair Information PracticesThe Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:We will notify you via email• Within 7 business daysWe also agree to the Individual Redress Principle which requires that individuals have the right to legally pursue enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.CAN SPAM ActThe CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.We collect your email address in order to:• Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions• Process orders and to send information and updates pertaining to orders.• Send you additional information related to your product and/or service• Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred.To be in accordance with CANSPAM, we agree to the following:• Not use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.• Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.• Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.• Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.• Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.• Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.• Follow the instructions at the bottom of each email.If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can contact us at info@ribbonmics.com or unsubscribe here and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.Changes to this Privacy PolicyWe may update this Privacy Policy from time to time by posting a new version online. You should check this page occasionally to review any changes. If we make any material changes we will notify you by posting the revised Privacy Policy on our Website. This helps you to always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances, if any, it is disclosed. Your continued use of the Website will be subject to the terms of the then-current Privacy Policy.Contacting UsIf there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.Audio Engineering Associates1029 N. Allen AvePASADENA, CA 91104United Statesinfo@ribbonmics.com626-798-9128Last Edited on May 25, 2018
